[ Bells chiming ]
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ Silent night , holy night ♪
♪ All is dark , save the light ♪
♪ Shining where the mother mild ♪
♪ Watches over the holy child ♪
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
[ Dog barking ]
♪ Silent night ♪
[ Dog continues barking ]
♪ Jingle bells , jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh , what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
♪ Jingle bells , jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh , what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
[ Party-goers chattering ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Party-goers laughing ]
[ Party-goers chattering ]
[ Heavy breathing continues ]
[ Party-goers laughing ]
Hey , who left the goddamn front door open ?
[ Door closes ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Party-goers chattering ]
[ Heavy breathing continues ]
[ Woman laughing ]
Oh , by the way , how come I
was the only one there working tonight ?
We were there this afternoon , Barb .
A likely story .
- How 's it look ? - Yule-ish , very Yule-ish .
Have you got your Santa Claus suit ready ?
Yeah . What time the little bastards arrive ?
- BARB : At one o 'clock . - Terrific !
[ Phone ringing ]
Hello ?
Pardon ?
Who ?
Barb , it 's for you . Long distance .
Oh , great . Hang on , I 'll take it in the other room .
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Floor creaking ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Wind howling ]
[ Laughter ]
Could you guys shut up in there ? I can 't hear a damn thing !
- [ Party-goers shouting ] - Hello ?
Mom , hang on , I can 't hear you .
Operator , I can 't hear ...
what 's coming from the other end .
Can you ... ? Yeah . All right , let 's see .
WOMAN : Party 's over ! Come on , all the men out !
Come on ! Bye-bye !
BARB : No , operator , I still can 't hear .
[ Door creaking ] [ Heavy breathing ]
Hi , Mommy ! I can hear you now .
No , we 're just having a little party .
No , I 've had a couple .
BARB : Oh , come on , I 'm not drunk .
No , no . Um , I have some stuff to do in the afternoon ,
and then I was just gonna get the seven twenty train
into the city .
No !
WOMAN : Goodnight ! Bye !
[ Woman laughing ]
Oh , come on . You got to be kidding !
Why can 't I come , too ?
BARB : Well , who the hell is he ?
Good night .
BARB : You 're a real gold-plated whore , Mother ,
- you know that ? - See you next week .
Okay .
Hey , call before you come .
I 'm gonna have to get my parents used to that .
BARB : I 'll just get a couple of my friends - -
- Okay . - ... and we 'll go , uh , skiing .
- WOMAN : Goodnight ! Bye ! - Yeah , sure . I 'll be fine .
I 'll see you around .
MAN : Hey , Chris , wait up ! I 'll give you a ride .
[ Engine starting outside ]
WOMAN : Put the Christmas music back on .
[ Door closing ]
" Hark ! The Herald Angels Sing " plays )
Anyone want to go skiing for a few days ?
Yeah , sure , Barb .
My mother 's taking a place up at Mount Holly 's .
Anyone else want to come ?
- Yeah , sounds like fun . - Great .
How ' bout you , Clare ?
Uh , no thanks , Barb . I 've made some other plans .
[ Scoffs ]
[ Phone ringing ]
I 'll get it .
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
Hey , quiet !
It 's him again ! The moaner !
[ " Hark ! The Herald Angels Sing " continues ]
Shh !
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Garbled noises ]
He 's expanded his act .
Could that be one person ?
No , Clare , that 's the Mormon Tabernacle Choir
doing their annual obscene phone call .
Shh !
[ Screaming ]
[ Whispering ] CALLER : Let me lick it !
Let me stick my tongue on it and lick it !
[ Chuckles ]
[ Snorting ]
[ Laughing ] You ...
You pig cunt !
Yeah , you pig cunt ! You pig cunt !
Let me lick it ! Lick it !
Lick it !
Let me lick your pretty piggy cunt !
[ Laughing ]
Pretty pig cunt !
I 'll lick your pretty pig clit . I 'm like a tuna farm , baby !
Mmm , not bad .
CALLER : Suck my juicy cock !
I 'll come over .
I 'll come over and you can - - you can suck it . Suck it ! Okay ?
Listen , you pervert !
Why don 't you go over to Lambda Chi ?
They could use a little of this .
CALLER : You piggy cunt ,
you want my fat cock .
Oh , why don 't you go find a wall socket
and stick your tongue in it , that 'll give you a charge .
CALLER : I 'll stick my tongue up your pretty pussy !
You fucking creep !
CALLER : I 'm going to kill you .
[ Disconnect tone ]
[ " Hark ! The Herald Angels Sing " ends ]
[ Sighs ]
Well , Super Tongue strikes again .
Fastest tongue in the west .
That was sick !
I really don 't think you should provoke
somebody like that , Barb .
Oh , listen , this guy 's minor league .
In the city , I get two of those a day .
Maybe .
But you know that town girl was raped a couple of weeks ago .
Darling ...
you can 't rape a Townie !
CLARE : You really are too much , Barb .
Oh , come on , this is a sorority house ,
not a convent !
[ " Jingle Bells " plays ]
I 'll see ya later . I 'm gonna go pack .
Come on , Clare . She didn 't mean anything .
No , really , Jess , it 's okay . I have to finish packing anyway .
Hasn 't she had enough trouble fitting in here without you
getting at her all the time ?
Come on .
I know a professional virgin when I see one !
WOMAN : Hey , can I get a hand out here ?
Speaking of professional virgins ...
Here we have the Queen of Vaudeville circa 1891 .
[ Gasps ] Where have you been ?
I 've been shopping .
You know I think the store is
most spectacular at this time of year .
I never saw such a bunch of junk !
Mrs. Mac , come in the other room !
We 've got a surprise for you !
[ Excited chatter ]
There you are .
[ Meowing ]
Where have you been ?
Mrs. Mac 's been looking all over for you .
Oh , little puss ! Hello .
Go on , now !
Got some things to do .
Oh , let 's see .
[ Meowing ]
[ Continued meowing ]
- Claude ? - [ Meowing ]
Is that you , puss ?
Kitty ?
Who is that ?
Who is it ?
[ Meowing ]
Claude ?
Who is that ?
Who is it ?
[ Screaming ]
[ Chattering ]
Oh , girls ...
it 's really beautiful .
[ Chattering ]
It 's gorgeous and the color and everything .
No , it 's really lovely .
I 've got about as much use for this as a chastity belt !
[ Laughing ]
Aw , come on , Mrs. Mac , put it on .
Put it on ?
Oh , come on , I 'm not going to bed !
Come on , please .
Yeah , put it on !
Put it on .
Anything for you girls , because it 's Christmas .
Hey , you bet !
[ Chattering ]
[ Suspenseful music ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
MRS. MAC : Okay , girls , party 's over .
Let 's get this junk cleaned up , eh ?
Oh yeah , come on .
Everybody takes a little something ,
it won 't take long .
Come on , girls , just a little cooperation .
- [ Heavy breathing continues ] - [ Indistinct chattering ]
[ Door closes ]
Let 's just get you up , ' cause you 're tired .
You really are !
Good night .
[ Laughter ]
" B " for ...
booze .
There you are .
WOMEN : Good night , good night . Merry Christmas !
Jess , you girls are just too good to me .
Oh , nonsense , Mrs. Mac .
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
MAN : Hello , is Jess there , please ?
Yeah , wait a second , Peter .
Jess , it 's for you . It 's him .
Hello ?
PETER : Hi , how 's the party ?
Oh , it was good . Too bad you couldn 't make it .
PETER : I 've been - - I 've been practicing
for four days straight . I am really , really wiped out .
Yes , I know .
Jess , dear ...
You won 't forget to put out the lights ?
You 've got to find some time . I 've gotta talk to you .
PETER : You sound funny . What 's the matter ?
Nothing 's the matter . I just wanna talk to you .
PETER : Why don 't you tell me now ?
Because I wanna talk to you , face to face .
PETER : Jess , I haven 't been to bed in three nights .
I 'm just not the mood to be playing games .
Look , Peter , we 'll talk about it tomorrow , okay ?
PETER : Okay . I 'll be in Room 30 , all day .
All right , I 'll see you around two .
PETER : I didn 't mean to sound short with you .
I - - I guess I 'm just exhausted , okay ?
Yeah , it 's okay .
PETER : I love you .
I know .
See you tomorrow .
PETER : Yeah , well , good night .
[ Hangs up phone ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Humming while brushing ]
[ Sniffs ]
[ Spits ]
Jesus , I wouldn 't wear this to have my liver out !
[ Knocking ]
Clare ?
[ Chair creaking ]
CALLER : ♪ Little baby Bunting ♪
♪ Daddy 's gone a-huntin ' ♪
♪ Gone to fetch a rabbit skin ♪
♪ To wrap his baby Agnes in ♪
[ Bells chiming ]
[ Bicycle bell ringing ]
[ Car horn honking ]
[ Children chattering ]
[ Bicycle bell ringing ]
[ Laughing ]
- Oh , thank you . - That 's okay .
I 'm sorry . I should have been keeping a better watch
on them .
I should think so .
Yeah , well , I said I was sorry .
Excuse me ?
I hate to bother you . I can see that you 're busy .
But I wonder if you could help me .
You see , I was supposed to meet my daughter here
at one o 'clock .
It 's - - it 's half past now , and she 's still not here .
Her name 's Clare Harrison . Do you know her ?
Clare Harrison ?
Yeah , I think so .
I know she lives in a sorority house .
It 's - - it 's called , um ...
Pi , uh , Kappa Sig - -
Oh , of course ! Yeah , well , Kappa 's our sister sorority .
Uh , some of the girls are over here today ,
but I haven 't seen Clare .
Uh , the place isn 't far . I 'll tell you how to get there .
Ho , ho , ho , shit !
Santa ! Please .
Look , she 's supposed to be going away with me
for the weekend , goddammit .
Well , we decided that we would go skiing for a few days .
Yeah , and I 've been looking forward to this
for three weeks . Bitch !
Isn 't Santa naughty ?
Ho , ho , ho , fuck .
MRS. MAC : I just don 't know , Mr. Harrison .
Her clothes are all packed and ready to go .
I 'll bet you 'll find her over at the common room .
They 're having a party there today
for underprivileged children .
[ Bells chiming ]
Yes , I know .
I 'm very disappointed in this atmosphere ,
and I intend to do something about it .
Who 's this ?
Um , uh , that 's , uh , a friend of Clare 's ,
a very nice young man from the town .
Uh , Chris Hayden .
I didn 't send my daughter here to be drinking and
picking up boys .
Oh , Clare is a good girl , Mr. Harrison .
I wouldn 't want you to get the wrong idea about that .
She is a good girl .
I 'm sure you 'll find her at the fraternity house .
As a matter of fact , I could show you the way .
I-I have to go to a store near there .
If you wouldn 't mind giving me a lift .
I know where it is .
But I 'll be glad to give you a ride .
[ Sighs ]
This is very kind of you , Mr. Harrison .
I 'll just get my bag .
" I didn 't send my daughter here to be drinking
and picking up boys . "
Tough shit !
I 'm just supposed to be responsible ...
for the morals of every girl in this goddamn house ?
These broads would hump the Leaning Tower of Pisa ,
if they could get up there .
I do my best .
I don 't know what the bastards expect of me .
Christ 's sake !
[ Meowing ]
Claude ?
Is that you , Claudekins ?
Here Kitty , Kitty , kitty , kitty , Kitty !
Come on , Claude . Come say goodbye to Mommy !
[ Meowing ]
Is that you , Claude ?
Oh , Jesus !
Claude , look what you made me do !
Balls !
Come on , Claude !
Here Kitty , Kitty , kitty , kitty , Kitty !
Come on , Claude ! I gotta go !
Here , kitty !
Oh , goddammit , Claude ! You little prick !
This is very kind of you , Mr. Harrison .
Think nothing of it .
[ Dog barking ]
♪ ♪
JESS : I 'm pregnant .
PETER : What ?
PETER : God , Jess , that 's fantastic !
I don 't want it .
You don 't want it ?
No .
I 'm going to have an abortion .
You can 't make a decision like that .
You haven 't even asked me .
I wasn 't even gonna tell you .
Jess .
I want us to have a baby .
- Peter , I can 't ! - Oh , Christ , Jess .
Don 't you ever consider anyone but yourself ?
I 've thought this out very carefully ,
and I know what I 'm gonna do .
Do you know how important this afternoon is to me ?
Yes , I do .
Why don 't you just get out of here .
[ Footsteps stomping ]
Jess !
I want to talk to you tonight .
There 's nothing to discuss , Peter !
I think there is !
I 'm not gonna change my mind !
We 'll see .
Will you be there at nine o 'clock ?
Yes .
Okay , I 'll see you tonight .
[ Door closing ]
Yes , dear .
I 'm sure there 's nothing wrong .
Yes , I 've just been talking with a friend of hers .
She 's going to call around for me .
Here , need some more , huh ?
Yes , well , if we don 't have any luck , I 'll go to the police .
[ Laughs ]
Yes .
Well , I don 't think I 'll be home tonight .
It 's a bit late to head out now .
I think the lil ' bugger 's schnockered ,
son of a bitch .
- Eh , Shortie ? - Yeah , goodbye , dear .
- [ Laughs ] - You are , aren 't ya ?
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
Oh hell , not again !
WOMAN : Billy !
Billy ? [ Sighs ]
I 'm sorry , you have the wrong number .
CALLER : What your mother and I must know is ...
Where did you put the baby ?
You 've got the wrong number .
WOMAN : Where did you put Agnes , Billy ?
MAN : Billy .
Look , I 'm telling you , you have the wrong number !
WOMAN : What your mother and I must know is - -
Billy !
[ Bell ringing ]
BARB : You guys can never get it together with a - -
PHYL : Look , I really don 't think
you 're taking this as seriously
as you should . I mean , honestly .
MAN : We may hear a non specific - -
Hold it , hold it ! Jesus !
Could you just give it to me one at a time ?
Well , what the hell are you planning to do about it ?
You ... shut up !
You know , for a public servant ,
I think your attitude really sucks .
Shut up .
Now , Mr. Harrison ,
if you 're convinced your daughter is missing ,
you can fill out one of these forms .
I don 't know if it 's any consolation ,
but 90 percent of the time
girls who are reported missing from the college ,
they 're at a cabin somewhere , with a boyfriend .
Thanks , but that 's not much consolation .
Oh , here , Mrs. Mac , let me help .
Thank you , dear .
You know , we got to get Mr. Reynolds
to fix this door .
I must have called that son of a bitch
a hundred times about it .
JESS : Oh , Mrs. Mac ,
there was another one of those calls just now .
Oh , was there , dear ?
JESS : It was weird !
Some woman screaming , then a man wailing .
Uh , Clare Harrison 's father was here today .
JESS : Oh , really ?
I 'm sorry I didn 't get to say goodbye to her .
Well , you still might .
Clare didn 't meet him where she was supposed to .
Uh , I thought she went over to the fraternity .
Where is it ?
[ Mrs. Mac mumbling ]
Eureka !
Shit !
[ Phone ringing ]
Excuse me .
Could you give me the number of the sorority house ?
Please .
Yeah , sure .
It 's , uh ...
Fellatio ... 2-0-8-8-0 .
What ?
Fellatio .
It - - It 's a - - it 's a new exchange .
" F " - " E " .
That 's a new one on me .
How do you spell it ?
Capital ' F ' , ' E ' ,
little ' L ' , ' L ' ,
' A ' , ' T ' , ' I ' , ' O ' .
Thanks .
Don 't mention it .
[ Hockey sticks smacking pucks ]
[ Knocking ]
Chris !
Break !
Hi , what 's up ?
- Have you seen Clare today ? - No , she went home .
No she didn 't . No one knows where she is .
Are you serious ?
I thought maybe she was with you
or at least you might have heard from her .
No , not since last night .
Well , her father came to pick her up
at 1 o 'clock today , and she didn 't show .
So he went down to the police station
with Phyl and Barb .
What happened ?
- They didn 't take it seriously . - Why ?
I don 't know .
I think they figured she was shacked up somewhere .
[ Piano music playing ]
[ Stops playing piano ]
Well , um , she 's out for Christmas holidays , but ...
there was a band practice over at the high school
this afternoon , and ...
Janice plays the clarinet ,
and , uh , when she didn 't come home ,
I-I phoned Melody Green , that 's her ... best friend .
And , uh , they hadn 't seen her all day .
She 's only 13 years old , Lieutenant ,
and ... my husband 's a trucker , he 's out on the road ,
and so I came over here .
Yeah , well , is it really so unusual
for her to be just a few hours late , Mrs. Quaife ?
Oh , yes . She should have been home at noon .
We were gonna buy a present for her father .
[ Door slams open ]
Nash , you stupid son of a bitch , you got a big goddamn mouth !
What the hell are you talking about ?
LIEUTENANT : Hi Chris , how 's your brother ?
Ken , I gotta talk to you .
What 's up ?
I want to know why nothing 's being done
about Clare Harrison being missing ,
and why this ... idiot gets away with saying
the things he does ?
You 're a friend of Clare Harrison ?
Yeah , I 've been taking her out .
Oh , this is Jess , Ken .
She lives in the same sorority house as Clare .
All right , come on in .
Sergeant , bring me the file on the Harrison girl .
And take care of this .
[ Phone ringing ]
I do wish you 'd try to eat something , Mr. Harrison .
You know , starving yourself isn 't going to help
the situation at all .
No , thank you very much , Mrs. MacHenry ,
but I just have no appetite .
I feel I should be doing something ,
but I don 't know what .
Well , why don 't you just try to stop worrying ?
The best thing you can do is stay right here .
I 'm sure she 'll call or show up soon .
If I just knew what to do .
Did you know ... it 's a very little known fact ,
but ... did you know that
there is a certain species of turtle ...
tha - -
There 's a certain species of turtle ...
that can screw for three days without stopping .
You don 't believe me , do you ?
Well , I mean how could I make something like that up ?
Uh , Barb , dear , I - - I - - 1 ...
No , really , they just three days , 24 hours a day .
Whoomp ! Whoomp !
Can you believe that ? Three days ?
I 'm lucky if I get three minutes .
Do you know how I know this ?
Because I went down to the zoo , and I watched them .
It was very boring .
Well , actually , um , I , uh , didn 't stay
for the whole three days .
I went over and I watched the zebras ,
because they only take 30 seconds .
Premature ejaculation !
[ Laughing ]
[ Gags ]
[ Coughing ]
You think it 's my fault , don 't you ?
Barb , stop it !
Don 't shit me !
It 's what you 're all thinking .
Why don 't you just come right out and say it ?
You think that I drove her away ...
and if she 's dead , you 're gonna blame me .
Barb , for God 's sake !
Well , that 's what we 're all thinking
why doesn 't someone just come right out and say it ?
Barb , dear , you 've had too much to drink .
Mr. Harrison - -
I don 't give a shit about Mr. Harrison !
I 'm sick and tired of everyone in this house insinuating stuff
and not coming out with what they mean .
Barb , why don 't you go upstairs and lie down for a while ?
Shut up !
And you leave me alone , goddamn you !
You think it 's my fault , don 't you ?
You 've been implying it all afternoon !
Barb , you 're drunk !
Go to bed !
[ Clock ticking ]
Yeah , sure . Fine .
[ Tossing piano top ]
[ Crash ]
- Any news ? - Yes ! Where 's Mr. Harrison ?
Uh , he-he 's in the dining room .
- [ Sirens ] - [ Dog barking ]
[ Inaudible Dialogue ]
[ Suspenseful music ]
- We won 't be long , Mrs. Mac . - All right , dear .
PHYL : See you later .
- Uh , Phyl ? - Yeah ?
Phyl , listen , I 'm sure Clare will be all right .
I hope so .
And I just want to tell you that
I 'm going to go to my sister 's for the holiday ...
so I might not be here when you get back .
That 's okay . Look , just check in on Barb before you leave ,
could you do that ?
Of course , I will . And you bundle up .
We 'll be all right , Mrs. Mac .
KEN : Mrs. Quaife ...
and Mr. Harrison have asked me to extend their thanks to you
for coming out on this cold night to help .
Now , Mrs. Quaife has told us that Janice most likely
came through this park ...
on her way home from school today .
So , the first thing we 'll do is comb the park .
When I tell you ,
I want you all to assemble on the south edge of the park
with your assigned officer .
Then , we 'll just walk through the park . Spread out evenly !
Don 't bunch up .
There 'll be two sets of dogs leading the way .
Just spread out and follow them .
George and Carly ...
stay out on the flanks .
The fumes " ll mess up the dogs ,
and don 't go more than ten miles an hour
or you 'll be no use to us .
Now if any of you find anything , I want you
to send someone out immediately to report it to me .
Is that clear ?
Are there any questions ?
Okay , let 's go .
[ Snowmobiles starting up ]
[ Dogs barking ]
[ Dog barking ]
♪ Alligators come through the gate ♪
♪ But goodbye leg if ya get away late ♪
♪ Lollies always love to pop ♪
[ Purring ]
[ Car horn honking ]
All right ! I hear ya !
[ Meowing ]
Claude ?
Where are you ?
[ Meowing ]
♪ ♪
Claude ?
How did you get up in the attic , Claude ?
Gee !
[ Car horn honking ]
All right ! Goddammit ! You can wait !
[ Door opening , creaking ]
Claude , are you up here ?
Jesus Christ , I don 't see how you could be up here .
Claude !
[ Groans ]
Jesus , Claude !
Now look at what you made me do !
Snagged my stocking ...
Oh , Jesus , I 've got to clean this place up
one of these days .
Claude !
Claude ?
I can 't see a damn thing .
Goddammit , Claude ! I 'm gonna have you fixed !
[ Gasps ]
[ Wood creaking ]
[ Yells ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasping ]
Hey !
Anybody there ?
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Dogs barking ]
I 'm gonna have to split .
Peter 's coming around , and I 'm late already .
- My God , it 's cold . - We 'll coming home soon , too .
- I 'm freezing . - Oh , God . Okay , see you .
We 'll let you know if anything happens .
[ Dogs barking ]
♪ ♪
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming continues ]
[ Dogs barking ]
- Janice ! Is that my baby ? - Take it easy , Mrs. Quaife !
Janice ! Janice !
No !
Janice ! Janice , Janice !
Janice ! Janice ! Janice !
Janice !
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
[ Garbled crying ]
Who is this ?
CALLER : Oh , help me ! Please , stop !
Oh , God , please ! Help me !
What do you want ? Why are you doing this ?
[ Screams ]
CALLER : Filthy Billy !
[ Indistinct yelling ]
Who are you ?
For God 's sake , what are you doing ?
CALLER : I know what you did , Billy !
Filthy Billy !
Billy ! Billy ! Mad !
Stop this !
[ Chuckling ]
Oh , Jesus Christ ! Mrs. Mac ?
Mrs. Mac , are you home ?
Mrs. Mac , are you up there ?
Yes , hello ?
Um , I 've been getting obscene phone calls ,
and I want to know what can be done about it .
Yes , all right . I 'll hold , but only for a moment .
[ Gasps ]
Peter , Jesus , you scared the hell out of me !
Why didn 't you say something ?
Yeah ? Well ...
you scared the hell out of me , too .
What was all that yelling about ?
I was upstairs having a little sleep .
Hope you don 't mind , but it got a little cold out there
waiting for you .
- Sorry , I was late , Peter . - Yeah .
Clare Harrison is missing .
I was out with the search party looking for her .
- Yes , hello ? - How noble .
I want to report something .
No , I don 't want to hold !
How did the recital go ?
How do you think it went ?
Peter , what kind of a game are you playing ?
I thought you wanted to talk .
So why don 't you quit attacking me
and we 'll try to have a rational , adult conversation ?
Yes , now stay on the line !
Okay ! Now calm down , lady . Let 's have the story .
- Oh , yeah ? What 's the address ? - [ Phone ringing ]
Six Belmont Street . How many calls ?
Well , did you call the phone company ?
Oh , yeah ?
Well , miss , we 're very busy here .
There 's been a child murdered in the park .
[ Phone ringing ]
I don 't know when we can get a man on it .
It 's probably just one of your boyfriends
playing a little joke .
Yeah . Well , I 'll report it and try to get a man on it
just as soon as possible .
I 'm sorry , Miss .
[ Sighs ]
[ Phone ringing ]
Jess , what 's wrong ?
A little girl was found murdered in the park .
What ?
The search party that was looking for Clare
found a little girl murdered .
And Clare 's still missing .
Look , Clare 's all right .
Is she ?
Now listen , Jess , I know you 're upset .
But I 've got something to tell you .
Mm-hmm .
I 'm leaving the conservatory .
- Peter . - Now , you just hear me out .
Will you hear me out , please ?
Now , I 've lived in one room for eight years ,
and I 'm tired of it .
I 'm tired of having to line up behind six people
every time I wanna take a bath . I 've had it .
I 'm quitting the conservatory , and we 're getting married .
Well , say something .
Do you remember when we first met ?
You told me about your wanting to be a concert pianist ,
how it was your greatest dream ,
and I told you about some of the things that
I wanted to do ?
I still want to do those things .
You can 't ask me to drop everything
I 've been working for
and give up all my ambitions , because your plans have changed .
Be realistic . I can 't marry you .
PETER : Sure you can .
What does it change ?
We could be married .
You could still do anything you wanted to do .
Peter , I don 't want to marry you .
All right .
What about the baby ?
I didn 't want to bother you with it , sir .
Well , you didn 't .
Six Belmont Street , that 's where your daughter lives ?
Yes , it is .
A high school girl 's been murdered .
Mr. Harrison 's daughter is missing .
And now at the house where she lives ,
the other girls are getting obscene phone calls .
[ Phone ringing ]
Don 't you think we ought to look into it , Nash ?
Well , Lieutenant , I guess , sure .
Thank you , Lieutenant .
Yeah , thanks Ken .
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Laughing ]
Sergeant Nash .
Could I speak to you for a minute ?
Yeah ... sure , Lieutenant .
[ Laughing ]
What 's this ?
That 's the number at the sorority house .
Fellatio ?
Yeah , it 's the new exchange , " F " - " E " .
[ Laughing ]
The new exchange ?
Yeah , fellatio .
One of the girls that was in this afternoon gave it to me .
She gave it to you ?
Yeah .
Nash , I don 't think you could pick your nose
without written instructions .
[ Laughing ]
I know . Something dirty , ain 't it ?
[ Ornaments breaking ]
You selfish bitch .
You 're talking about killing our baby
as though you were having a wart removed .
Now , can you see why I didn 't want to tell you ?
What the hell are you trying to do to me ?
What are you doing to yourself ?
Jess ,
let 's get one thing straight .
You are not going to abort that baby .
Peter , you 're not gonna tell me what I can and cannot do .
Jess , if you try getting an abortion - -
I think you 'd better leave !
If you try getting an abortion - -
I said get out !
You 're gonna be very sorry .
[ Dog barking ]
Hi , Peter .
[ Door slams shut ]
I 'll get Jess .
- Jess , are you okay ? - Yeah , I 'm okay .
Any more news ?
No , but there 's some people here
to see about the phone calls .
Jess , this is Lieutenant Fuller , and , I 'm sorry .
Uh , Graham , Bill Graham .
Are you the person who called the station today ?
Yes .
I would like to put a tap on your phone .
But we 'll need your written permission
to do that if it 's okay with you ?
- Okay . - Okay , Graham ,
You can go ahead .
And I 'd like to see Clare Harrison 's room .
- Sure . - Where 's the telephone ?
Uh , there 's one in the living room
and one here in the hallway .
Clare 's room is up here .
How many girls live in this house ?
Uh , usually ten .
Hello , this is Lineman Graham , at Six Belmont .
I 'm working line 559-6114 .
Great .
This afternoon , I got a call
from a woman that I thought was a wrong number .
But then she started screaming at me .
Who was the last one here to see Miss Harrison ?
- I think I was . - When , approximately ?
Last night , about 10 : 30 .
Is this the way she left her room ,
as far as you know ?
Yes .
What 's this ?
We were having a party last night .
She drink a lot ?
No , hardly at all .
Does she have any emotional problems ,
anything like that ?
PHYL : No , not Clare .
Who was she seeing besides Chris Hayden ?
- No one . - Sure of that ?
So , you were the last one to see her
sometime this morning ?
- Last night . - Right , last night .
Well , did anyone see her this morning ?
- No . - I didn 't .
And all the other girls have gone for the holidays .
Can I get a list of their phone numbers
where I can reach them ?
Sure . There 's one in Mrs. Mac 's room .
- Who 's Mrs. Mac ? - She 's the house mother .
Is there anyone else in the house right now ?
Yes , another girl , Barbara Coard .
She 's upstairs asleep . Um , she 's not feeling too well .
Is she the one that was at the station today ?
- Yeah . - Yeah , well , let her sleep .
Okay .
Were there any deliveries yesterday ?
Or was anyone working in the house ,
anything like that ?
No , I don 't think so . Mrs. Mac would know .
Is her sister 's number on this list ?
Yes .
Graham , how 's it going ? You about finished ?
Yeah . What I 've done is , I 've tapped this phone ,
so that when it rings ,
it 'll ring at the station house , too .
At the same time ,
I 'll be at the phone company checking on the location
of the source of the call .
Are there any other phones in the house ?
Yes , the house mother has a line .
Yeah , but it 's another number ,
and there haven 't been any calls on it .
You 're gonna have to keep this guy
on the line as long as possible .
We got a mechanical system here and it takes a while .
I know it 's not very pleasant . But - -
Uh , girls , can I show you something ?
- FULLER : See the car outside ? - PHYL : Yeah .
FULLER : We got one of our men in it ,
so you 've got nothing to worry about .
Yeah , sure .
[ Dog barking ]
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Phyl sobbing ] Oh , God , Jess .
I just know Clare is dead . I can just feel it .
Oh , come on now , Phyl , we don 't know that .
Poor Mr. Harrison ! I feel so sorry for him !
Hey , hey .
How 's Chris ?
Oh , he 's okay . You know Chris .
Oh , God .
I 'm sorry , Jess .
[ Sighs ]
PHYL : I guess I 'm just exhausted .
I 've been taking these pills for my cold
and they knock me out .
[ Sighs ]
Will you be okay if I go up to bed ?
Yes , of course .
Are you sure ?
Yes , go up and get some rest .
Call me if there 's any news .
I will .
Thanks .
- Good night , Phyl . - Good night .
♪ ♪
Yeah , everything clear on your end Jeff ?
- [ Phone ringing ] - Okay . Sure . Uh , yeah .
Now look , I 'm gonna need about 10 more minutes .
Now be sure you tell those people again
they gotta keep this guy on the line .
- [ Phone ringing ] - Right .
' Cause he hasn 't worn his hat for the last two days .
Yes , we certainly will look into that .
Thank you very much .
Jesus !
Graham 's nearly ready at the switching station .
Now , when the phone rings at the house there ,
this one will ring , too .
The transmitters have been removed ,
so , uh , we won 't pick anything up at all
from this end .
Great , thanks .
Lieutenant , the men are here from Scarborough .
Okay .
♪ ♪
[ Heavy breathing ]
CALLER : ♪ ... went a-hunting ♪
♪ To fetch a rabbit skin ♪
[ Sobbing ]
[ Typewriter clacking ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Door creaking ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Wood creaking ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Barb gasping ]
Barb , what 's the matter ?
[ Gasping continues ]
- Easy , relax . You 'll be okay . - [ Continues gasping ]
It 's okay .
I gue - - I gue - - I guess I had a - - a nightmare !
I dreamed a stranger ... was coming in my room .
I guess that 's what gave me asthma , huh ?
Take it easy , it 's all right now .
Just relax .
[ " O Come , All Ye Faithful " being sung outside ]
BARB : I should be so lucky
to have a stranger come in my room .
♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ O come ye , O come ye to Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come and behold him ♪
♪ Born the King of Angels ♪
♪ O come , let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
♪ Sing , choirs of angels ♪
[ Heavy breathing ]
♪ Glory in the highest ♪
♪ O come , let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
♪ Yea , Lord , we greet thee ♪
CALLER : Agnes .
Agnes , it 's me , Billy .
It 's all right , Agnes ! It 's all right . Shh !
Pretty Agnes .
♪ Word of the Father ♪
Agnes , don 't you tell what we did , Agnes ...
Agnes .
[ Groans ]
♪ ... let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
[ Glass breaking ] [ Gasping ]
[ Clapping ]
Jean !
What 's up ?
Jean , get the children in the car .
What 's going on ?
Please , just get them into the car !
Okay , kids , let 's go !
Come along children , hurry !
Miss , Miss !
Thank you . Merry Christmas .
There was a little girl murdered over in the park tonight .
- [ Phone ringing ] - Yes , I heard .
Your phone 's ringing .
[ Police radio chatter ]
Oh yes , excuse me . Good night .
Certainly . Good night .
Testing .
MAN : Bill Graham . Trace call coming in on front nine .
[ Phone ringing ]
Hello ?
[ Soft whine ]
JESS : Hello ? Who 's there ?
[ Machines clacking ]
[ Whining ]
- CHILD 'S VOICE : No , Billy , no ! - MAN 'S VOICE : Shit !
- MAN 'S VOICE : Tonight ! - WOMAN 'S VOICE : No , Billy !
- MAN 'S VOICE : Tonight ! - CHILD 'S VOICE : No , Billy !
[ Whining ]
WOMAN 'S VOICE : What your mother and I must know , eh ?
You know that ?
[ Machines clacking ]
Just like having a wart removed .
- Oh , my God ! - [ Disconnect tone ]
[ Machine stops ]
[ Disconnect tone ]
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Picks up phone ]
Hello ?
Jess , we didn 't get him .
There wasn 't enough time .
You 'll have to keep him on the line longer .
Oh , I see .
When you said , um , " Oh , my God , " did you recognize something ?
No , I guess it was just kind of getting to me .
Um , when he called before ,
did he use more than one voice like this ?
Yes , yes , he did .
He used several different voices .
Okay .
I meant to ask you tonight , uh , who was the guy
that was leaving when I arrived at your house ?
- JESS : My boyfriend , Peter . - Were you having a fight ?
MAN : What a goddamn asshole !
[ Indistinct chattering ]
Jess , I 'll have to call you back in a little while .
Are you all right ?
I 'll call you back in a little while ,
and we 'll - - we 'll get him next time .
- Bernie ! - Yup ?
Call a doctor .
I 'm not lettin ' no son of a bitch
trespass on my land in the middle of the night !
I don 't care what kind of a uniform he wears !
- What the hell is going on here ? - He fired on a police officer .
You 're goddamn right !
I 'd do it again , too ! The bastard was trespassing !
Cogan got an assful of birds hot .
Yeah , I 'm gonna make the son of the bitch
pick every one of ' em out with his teeth .
The next time , you 're gonna get the gun up your ass !
Sideways !
If you laugh , Buchanan , I 'll bust you to boy scout , I swear !
[ Laughing ]
If you think it was Peter , then why didn 't you
just tell the police ?
Well , because I 'm not really sure .
Well , he should be stopped .
Whoever it is should be stopped .
God , Jess , I haven 't had a minute 's sleep around here .
There 's been so much noise in the house .
What the hell was all that yelling about ?
Barb had an asthma attack . She was having a nightmare .
PHYL : Is she all right ?
JESS : Yes , she 's fine . She 's sleeping now .
He repeated almost word for word what Peter said to me tonight .
PHYL : Couldn 't it just be a coincidence ?
Oh God , Phyl , I don 't know .
I 'm so confused .
Oh , look , Jess , I really don 't think it could be Peter .
You know , I don 't like Peter much ,
but I don 't think he 's that sick .
I can 't believe Peter would do this .
He 's so gentle most of the time .
Oh , God , Phyl ! You know , I 'm really getting scared ?
Look , are you sure that cop 's still out there ?
Yep , he 's there .
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
PETER : Jess ?
Yes ?
PETER : Oh , God , please help me .
Oh look , Peter , don 't cry .
We can straighten things out .
There 's nothing to get so upset about .
[ Machines clacking ]
[ Phone ringing ]
- Yeah ? - It 's Bill Graham .
You want me to trace that one ?
Yeah , try and get it .
Right .
PETER : Jess , Jess !
We can 't kill the baby ! Please , Jess !
We can 't kill the baby !
[ Machines clacking ]
Peter , where are you ?
PETER : Please , Jess !
You know how I feel about the baby .
Don 't do this .
PETER : Jess , don 't hurt the baby !
- JESS : Stop this , Peter . - PETER : You want our baby ...
I know you do . I don 't want to hurt this baby .
Jess , please !
Peter , please tell me where you are .
[ Machines clacking ]
Shit !
[ Disconnect tone ]
I 'm sorry .
Yeah , the calls just aren 't long enough !
Right .
[ Phone ringing ]
Yes ?
Jess , Lieutenant Fuller .
Do you want to tell me what that 's all about ?
- You listened to that ? - KEN : Yes .
What did he mean about killing the baby ?
[ Police radio chatter ]
Jess , it 's important that you tell me .
I 'm pregnant .
I told him I didn 't want to have the baby .
When did you tell him this ?
JESS : Today .
Just today ? You 're sure ?
JESS : Yes .
KEN : " We can 't kill the baby " ,
that 's a strange way of putting it .
JESS : Peter 's an artist . He 's very high strung .
Neurotic , maybe ?
No .
No more than a lot of people .
KEN : Jess , are you telling me the truth ?
I 've got a feeling you 're holding something back from me .
Now , I don 't want it to be Peter .
But if it is , he needs help .
Do you know what I mean ?
The sooner , the better .
KEN : Now , look , think back .
Was Peter with you any of the times
that you got one of these calls ?
Yes !
Yes , he was here !
He was at the house tonight when the first call came !
That 's right ! It couldn 't be Peter !
Phyl , it couldn 't be Peter ! He was here !
Well , he 's obviously upset about something .
I 'd like to talk to him .
KEN : Can you tell me where I might reach him ?
Uh , well , he lives at Baker House .
Uh , but when he gets like this , he usually goes down
to the Recital Hall
at the Music Conservatory and plays .
Look , Jess , if you get any more calls ,
you 're gonna have to keep him on the line longer .
You 're not giving us enough time to get a trace .
I 'm trying , you know , it really upsets me .
KEN : Alright , of course . Look , you 're doing fine .
I 'll talk to you later .
Okay .
Thank God !
I knew it couldn 't have been Peter .
Well , what can I tell you ?
We covered the entire campus area .
They 're working their way toward the lake now .
Where do we go from there ?
Start ' em out on the south end of town ,
have them work their way through town
on a house-to-house .
[ Dog barking ]
Jess , do you want one aspirin or two ?
- JESS : Two , please . - Okay !
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Dog barking ]
PHYL : Jess ! Jess !
What are you doing ?
Some kind of a search party .
Yes ?
MAN : Sorry to scare you , Miss , but we 're with the search party .
Well , what do you want ?
Well , we wondered if you 'd seen anything peculiar tonight .
Well , not until you got here .
Well , they scared the shit out of me !
Sorry , miss , but you do know
there was a girl killed in the park tonight ?
Yes , we heard .
Well , we 're just helping the police
to look for the killer .
Well , we 'd ask you in , you know - -
But our dog died last night .
Oh , wow .
Well - - well , we don 't want to bother you
at a time like that .
Uh , we were just wondering if you noticed
anything suspicious here tonight ?
Oh , no . Sorry .
Well , you just keep your doors and windows locked ,
- and , uh , and you 'll be safe . - Okay .
- Do you understand ? - Thank a lot . We will .
And remember , there might be others
from the search party around .
So , don 't be afraid .
We 'll be around seeing that you 're safe .
Thank you very - -
Remember to lock those doors and windows , now .
- Okay , then . - Bye now .
- [ Dog barking ] - [ Growling ]
I 'd rather face the killer !
[ Laughing ]
Seriously , do you realize this is the only door and window
in this whole house that 's locked ?
Nash !
Get that Dean of Admissions on the phone .
Tell him I want all records on a " Peter Smythe , "
a music student ,
and have a car meet me out front .
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Door closes ]
♪ ♪
[ Knocking on door ]
Barb ? Are you awake ?
CALLER : Agnes .
[ Bells chiming ]
[ Door opening ]
[ Door closing ]
Phyl !
Are you there ?
[ Phone ringing ]
- Hello ? - CALLER : Hi !
[ Squeals ] You pig !
You fat pig !
You pig !
You bitch pig ! Look at your little baby !
CHILD 'S VOICE : No , Billy . No !
[ Chuckling ]
CHILD 'S VOICE : Ouch ! Help ! Help ! Help !
[ Machines clacking ]
WOMAN 'S VOICE : Billy !
Billy !
MAN 'S VOICE : Where 's the baby ? Where 's Agnes ?
You left Billy alone with Agnes !
- WOMAN 'S VOICE : Billy ! - MAN 'S VOICE : Where 's the baby ?
[ Yelling ]
MAN 'S VOICE : Where 's the baby ? Billy ! Billy !
[ Machines clacking ]
Lieutenant ! The guy 's on the phone again !
CALLER : Come on , Billy 's sick !
MAN 'S VOICE : I know you 're there ,
nasty Billy !
You answer me this minute !
CHILD 'S VOICE : Mommy !
Mommy !
- WOMAN 'S VOICE : Come here ! - CHILD 'S VOICE : Mommy !
WOMAN 'S VOICE : Where 's Agnes ?
[ Laughter ]
- MAN 'S VOICE : Agnes ! - [ Screaming ]
CHILD 'S VOICE : Give Mommy the baby !
Baby 's all right , Mommy !
You have to find her .
This is Graham . It 's group 140 , terminal 55 .
[ Caller singing indistinctly ]
CALLER : ... Agnes in .
- [ Disconnect tone ] - [ Sighs ]
NASH : Lieutenant Fuller ?
Yeah , Nash . What is it ?
NASH : Uh , phone company 's on the other line , sir .
They say they got a trace on this one .
Yeah , let 's have it .
NASH : He says the calls are coming
from number six , Belmont Street .
For chrisssakes , Nash , you got it wrong .
That 's where the calls are going into .
NASH : That 's where they 're coming from , too , sir .
♪ ♪
Oh , shit !
Jennings ?
Jennings !
Jennings , where the hell are you ?
Nash !
NASH : Yes , sir .
Look , I can 't get through to Jennings .
I want you to call that girl .
Nash , be calm .
Don 't tell her that the guy is in the house .
Just tell her to put down the phone
and walk straight out the front door .
I 'll be there in five minutes .
And Nash , if you blow this , I 'll kill you .
Phyl ?
Phyl ! Where are you ?
Please answer me !
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]
Hello ?
NASH : Who is this ?
It 's Jess .
Uh , Miss Bradford , uh , this is Sergeant Nash .
Are you the only one in the house ?
No . Phyl and Barb are upstairs asleep . Why ?
All right .
Now , I want you to do exactly what I tell you
without asking any questions , okay ?
No , no , no questions .
NASH : Now , just put the phone back on the hook ,
walk to the front door , and leave the house .
What 's wrong ?
Please , Miss Bradford , please just do as I tell you .
Okay . I 'll - - I 'll get Phyl and Barb .
No , no , no ! Don 't do that , Jess !
Jess , the caller is in the house !
NASH : The calls are coming from the house !
Jess !
NASH : Jess , get out ! And don 't go up there !
Don 't go upstairs , Jess !
Miss Bradford ! Miss Bradford !
Miss Bradford ?
Barb .
Phyl !
Barb !
JESS : Oh , please , answer me !
[ Panting ]
Phyl ! Barb ! Please , answer me !
Please , answer me !
Please ! Oh ! Oh !
[ Panting ]
♪ ♪
Barb ?
Phyl ?
[ Door rattling ]
[ Door opening ]
CALLER : Agnes .
Agnes , it 's me , Billy !
Agnes , Agnes , don 't you tell what we did , Agnes .
[ Caller Screaming ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Wood cracking ]
[ Continued yelling ]
[ Yelling stops ]
[ Panting ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Door closing ]
[ Wind howling ]
[ Panting ]
[ Water dripping ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Voice mumbling ]
Jess ?
Jess ? Are you all right ?
Jess , are you in there ?
[ Scraping ice off the window ]
Jess !
[ Glass breaking ]
[ Thud , glass crunching ]
Jess ?
[ Stepping on broken glass ]
Jess , is that you ?
Jess , are you in there ?
PETER : Jess ?
Jess , is that you ?
[ Metal clanking ]
Jess , why didn 't you answer me ?
What 's all the yelling about ?
Jess , you had me worried .
What are you doing down here ?
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming continues ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Breaking the door down ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
KEN : Jess ?
I knew it . I knew it in my gut .
It was that kid .
MAN : Why would Peter start killing people ?
KEN : I don 't know . He must 've made a call after - -
After each murder .
MAN : It 's hard to believe Jess would kill anybody ,
much less Peter !
MAN 2 : And she 's under .
KEN : How long do you think it 'll be before I
can talk to her ?
Just a couple questions .
MAN 2 : Well , she 'll be out for at least four hours ,
pretty groggy after that .
What time do her parents get here ?
KEN : A couple of hours .
They 're driving down from Unionville .
MAN 2 : I 'll stay with her till then .
With the condition she 's in ,
I wouldn 't count on talking to her
before tomorrow afternoon , if I were you .
Has anybody notified Patrick Cornell ?
- Who ? - Uh , Phyl 's boyfriend .
OFFICER : Hey , Mac , do you want us to check the attic and the basement ?
OFFICER 2 : Don 't touch anything till the state lab guys get here , I told you - -
Uh , Lieutenant ! I think we 're gonna have to take these bodies
to the morgue in Lincolnville .
The hospital doesn 't have
facilities to handle this many at one time .
All right , tell the coroner , they have to get started
on the autopsies right away .
Then notify the parents for identification .
Yes , sir .
Uh , I think that about wraps everything up here , sir .
Uh , state lab guys will be here in about an hour , they said .
[ Indistinct conversation ]
Uh , reporters , sir , and television news guys .
They want pictures .
Get them the hell out of here !
Tell them I 'll meet them down at the station , would you ?
OFFICER : All right , guys . C 'mon ! Move back downstairs !
[ Indistinct chattering ]
REPORTER : Is the Bradford girl being charged with - -
MAN : How ' bout a picture ?
KEN : All right , you guys . Come on , back off ! Back off !
Yes , the girl 's father 's upstairs
but he can 't tell you anything .
MAN 2 : Would you keep it down , please ?
We 've got a sick girl in here .
[ Indistinct conversation ]
KEN : Come on , get out ! [ indistinct ]
- OFFICER : Let 's go , come on ! - KEN : Come on , move it !
He 's in shock .
Help me get him downstairs . He 's got to go to a hospital .
You should be all right , Mr. Harrison .
She 's gonna be back ! I know it !
MAN : Okay , give us a hand , here .
MAN 2 : Hey you !
KEN : Nash , will you see that everything 's wrapped up ?
NASH : All right , Lieutenant , will do .
MAN : Hey , Lieutenant !
MAN 2 : Hey you ! Come on ! Out ! Out !
You want to spend the night in the can ? Move !
Jesus ! What 's the matter with this guy ?
MAN 3 : He 's suffering from shock .
We have to get him to the hospital .
Can you get us a car , Nash ?
- NASH : Yeah , yeah , let 's go ! - [ Door closing ]
NASH : All right , McCloskey ,
you heard what the Lieutenant said !
McCLOSKEY : Right .
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Clock ticking ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Indistinct singing ]
CALLER : Agnes !
It 's me , Billy !
[ Dog barking ]
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Phone continues ringing ]